"You shall die."
Okay, literal goosebumps. Look.
(Howard:)- What do you do?
- I draw my broadsword.
- I ready my quarter-staff.
- I drink my potion.
- I say we attack the big one.
- Give me the dice. I wanna roll.
(Howard:)The Dungeon Master's supposed to roll.
(Penny:)Yeah, well, I'm supposed to be in Vegas
throwing up on a shrimp buffet, give it.
(Penny:)- All right, what do I need?
- Uh, fifteen or higher.
Fifteen's the point. The point is 15. Give the
little lady some room. Here it is. Coming out.
- Sixteen! Yeah.
- Yeah.
(Penny:)Please tell me we're playing for money.
(Sheldon:)Oh, even better than money.
You gained experience points.
- More potion, please.
- Yeah.
- How are your crab cakes?
- Kind of funky.
- That's great.
- It is?
Does "funky" mean
something different in India?